{"Questions":[{"QuestionText":"Berlin is the capital of which country?","QuestionPoints":1,"Answers":[{"AnswerText":"Belgium","IsCorrect":false},{"AnswerText":"Netherlands","IsCorrect":false},{"AnswerText":"Germany","IsCorrect":true},{"AnswerText":"England","IsCorrect":false}]},{"QuestionText":"Does the moon have gravity?","QuestionPoints":1,"Answers":[{"AnswerText":"Yes — it’s 1.622 m/s²","IsCorrect":true},{"AnswerText":"No — there’s no gravity where you float","IsCorrect":false}]},{"QuestionText":"You want to make green paint. Which colors do you mix together?","QuestionPoints":1,"Answers":[{"AnswerText":"Red and yellow","IsCorrect":false},{"AnswerText":"Blue and yellow","IsCorrect":true},{"AnswerText":"Orange and purple","IsCorrect":false}]},{"QuestionText":"Which is the longest river in the world?","QuestionPoints":1,"Answers":[{"AnswerText":"Amazon","IsCorrect":false},{"AnswerText":"Nile","IsCorrect":true},{"AnswerText":"Mississippi","IsCorrect":false}]},{"QuestionText":"What language do most people in Austria speak?","QuestionPoints":1,"Answers":[{"AnswerText":"German","IsCorrect":true},{"AnswerText":"Austrian","IsCorrect":false},{"AnswerText":"Hungarian","IsCorrect":false}]},{"QuestionText":"Which country is closer to the North Pole?","QuestionPoints":1,"Answers":[{"AnswerText":"Finland","IsCorrect":true},{"AnswerText":"China","IsCorrect":false},{"AnswerText":"North Korea","IsCorrect":false}]},{"QuestionText":"On the “polar” opposite end of the world, which animal lives in Antarctica?","QuestionPoints":1,"Answers":[{"AnswerText":"Polar bear","IsCorrect":false},{"AnswerText":"Reindeer","IsCorrect":false},{"AnswerText":"Narwhals","IsCorrect":false},{"AnswerText":"Penguins","IsCorrect":true}]},{"QuestionText":"Who was president of the United States in 2005?","QuestionPoints":1,"Answers":[{"AnswerText":"Bill Clinton","IsCorrect":false},{"AnswerText":"Barack Obama","IsCorrect":false},{"AnswerText":"George W. Bush","IsCorrect":true},{"AnswerText":"George H.W. Bush","IsCorrect":false}]},{"QuestionText":"It takes a bright person to innovate! Who is credited with inventing the lightbulb?","QuestionPoints":1,"Answers":[{"AnswerText":"Alexander Graham Bell","IsCorrect":false},{"AnswerText":"Benjamin Franklin","IsCorrect":false},{"AnswerText":"Thomas Edison","IsCorrect":true}]},{"QuestionText":"Which of this countries held UEFA European Championship  in 2012?","QuestionPoints":1,"Answers":[{"AnswerText":"France","IsCorrect":false},{"AnswerText":"Ukraine","IsCorrect":true},{"AnswerText":"Egipt","IsCorrect":false},{"AnswerText":"Poland","IsCorrect":true}]}],"TotalPoints":10}